Your adoptive father told you
to get close to Yuwen Jingxuan
and take his life.
But look at you.
Please calm down, Master.
Luo Shuyan.
Don't forget
who bought you from the black market,
and who gave you a status and a life of luxury.
I know I was wrong.
Since you know you were wrong,
what will you do next?
Do you understand?
I understand.
Come out.
What's wrong?
Didn't you come to kill me?
Do it.
Just because I look like someone you know?
You don't just look like her.
You are her.
Perhaps this is what I owe you.
You died because of me.
So every time you come back to life,
you want to kill me.
Crazy.
Yes.
I am crazy.
But can you really bring yourself to kill me?
You are right.
Although I don't know why,
I really can't hurt you.
But I won't stay by your side either.
In an hour,
your acupoints will automatically unlock.
We will never meet again.
I can't just let her walk away like this.
Never see each other again?
In your dreams.
My sixth brother...
What kind of spell did he cast on Tang Zhiluo
to make her unable to kill him time and time again?
Calm down, Your Highness.
Fine.
He's not afraid of death, is he?
Then I will grant his wish.
But Lord Shang said...
I will explain it to my uncle.
I never do things without a backup plan.
According to our Rouran customs,
wedding clothes must be sewn by hand.
Do you not like it, Your Highness?
Oh.
Your craftsmanship is so good, Princess,
that I was mesmerized for a moment.
Try it on.
Does it fit, Your Highness?
It fits perfectly. Thank you, Princess Xiyao.
You have a fine build, Your Highness.
I still need to take in a few stitches here.
Actually, you don't have to be so nice to me, Princess.
We are allies,
and husband and wife.
It's only right that I treat you well.
Your Highness, after returning from court,
you spent half the day handling official documents,
and then took me on a tour of the entire manor.
Aren't you tired?
If it can really help you remember something,
I am willing to do anything.
Your Highness, don't forget
our agreement.
Seven days.
Within seven days,
if you still can't make me remember
the past,
you must let me leave the manor.
All right.
I really can't figure out
why Your Highness is doing these useless things.
Is it simply out of the goodness of your heart
to help an assassin, or...
Jingxuan.
All medicine has some toxicity.
Do you have a death wish?
Why isn't it working?
I take my medicine on time every day.
There's nothing wrong with the medicine.
There's something wrong with the person.
Could it be Miss Tang?
Impossible.
Stop talking.
Jingxuan.
Zhiluo.
I'll go get a doctor.
It's useless.
I used all my strength in that palm strike just now.
I clearly came here to kill you.
Zhiluo, Zhiluo.